http://www.gorhamsavingsbank.com/terms-of-use/

All branches are open for drive-up and appointment only. Call your branch to schedule an appointment. Drive-ups and video tellers will continue to be open with normal business hours. We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause.
Dismiss
Skip to content
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE.
Gorham Savings Bank (“GSB”) maintains this Site to provide you with information about GSB products and services and to facilitate communication with GSB. GSB may revise these terms and conditions from time to time.
GSB requires that all visitors to its site(s) on the Internet (the “Site”) adhere to the following rules and regulations. By accessing the Site, you indicate your agreement and acceptance of these terms and conditions.
Copyright in the images, text, screens, and web pages appearing at the Site is owned by GSB or others as indicated. The information and materials may not otherwise be copied, displayed, distributed, downloaded, licensed, modified, published, reposted, reproduced, reused, sold, transmitted, used to create a derivative work or otherwise used for public or commercial purposes, except as provided in these terms and conditions, without our express written permission.
Not all of the products or services described on the Site are available in all geographic areas. You may not be eligible for all the products or services described. GSB reserves the right to determine eligibility for any product or service.
Unless otherwise prohibited by law, any communication or material you transmit to us via the Site or Internet electronic mail is on a non-confidential basis, and GSB may use such communication or material for any purpose consistent with our Privacy Policy and applicable law, including reproduction, publication, broadcast and posting. GSB will use its best efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information on the Site, but it makes no warranties or representations as to the accuracy of the information. You agree that all access and use of the Site and its contents is at your own risk.
BY USING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT WE SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIM ANY LIABILITY (WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE) FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR SPECIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF THE SITE (EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), INCLUDING LIABILITY ASSOCIATED WITH ANY VIRUSES WHICH MAY INFECT A USER’S COMPUTER EQUIPMENT.
WITH REGARD TO SERVICES OR PRODUCTS PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SITE OR BY LINKAGE TO OTHER INTERNET SITES, EITHER DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY BY VARIOUS THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS OTHER THAN GSB, GSB MAKES NO WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY OR WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE WITH REGARD TO SUCH SERVICES AND PRODUCTS, AND GSB SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES WITH REGARD TO SUCH SERVICES AND PRODUCTS. GSB DOES NOT ENDORSE, AND SHALL HAVE NO OBLIGATION OR LIABILITY CONCERNING SUCH THIRD PARTY’S DELIVERY, OR NON-DELIVERY, OF THEIR RESPECTIVE SERVICES, PRODUCTS AND MATERIALS, OR THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS OR TIMELINESS THEREOF.
You agree that your use of this Site shall be governed by Maine law and agree that jurisdiction and venue shall be located in Cumberland County, Maine.
1. GENERAL PROVISIONS.
GSB does not represent or endorse the accuracy or reliability of any information, content or advertisements (the “Materials”) contained on, distributed through, or linked, downloaded or accessed from the Site, except as otherwise expressly stated in any applicable Service Agreement, nor the quality of any Software or other products, information or other materials displayed, purchased, or obtained by you as a result of any advertisement or any information or offer in or in connection with the Service or the Site (the “Products”). You acknowledge that any reliance upon any Service, Product, or Material shall be at your sole risk, except as otherwise required by applicable consumer protection law. GSB reserves the right, in its sole discretion and without any obligation, to correct any error or omission in any portion of any Service, Product, or Material.
2. LINKED INTERNET WEB SITES.
GSB has provided these internet links for your convenience. GSB does not endorse or accept responsibility for any such web site. GSB makes no representations about any web site you may access through GSB’s Site. Any web site linked to this Site is independent from GSB. As a result, GSB has no control over the Products, Services, Materials, or other information contained in or available through these third party web sites. The quality and dependability of these third party web sites may vary as they are updated or altered. Access to any other web sites linked to the Site is at your own risk.
3. DISCLOSURE OF ACCOUNT OR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES.
GSB maintains procedures designed to protect confidential information about you and your use of any materials, products and services. Please contact GSB to obtain a copy of GSB’s Privacy Statement for more information on GSB’s use of your personal information and account information provided or held by GSB
4. NO WARRANTIES.
YOU AGREE THAT GSB, ANY THIRD PARTY PROVIDER, AND ANY VENDOR SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY, CONTINGENT OR OTHERWISE, FOR THE ACCURACY OR TIMELINESS OF THE SERVICE OR PRODUCT OR THE ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, COMPLETENESS OR CORRECT SEQUENCING OF THE MATERIALS, OR FOR ANY DECISION MADE OR ACTION TAKEN BY YOU IN RELIANCE UPON THE PRODUCTS, MATERIALS OR THE SERVICE, OR FOR INTERRUPTION OR DELAY OF ANY DATA, MATERIAL, OR ANY OTHER ASPECT OF THE SERVICE. THIS SERVICE AND ALL PRODUCTS AND MATERIALS, ARE PROVIDED “AS IS”. THERE IS NO WARRANTY THAT ANY SERVICE, PRODUCTS, MATERIALS OR OTHER CONTENT AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH THIS WEB SITE, OR GSB’S COMPUTER SYSTEM, WILL FULFILL ANY OF YOUR PARTICULAR PURPOSES OR NEEDS. THERE ARE NO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR QUALITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE, OR ACCURACY OF INFORMATION CONTENT, AND NO OTHER WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, REGARDING THE PRODUCTS OR MATERIALS, OR ANY ASPECT OF THE SERVICE (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, INFORMATION ACCESS AND ORDER EXECUTION), EVEN IF GSB HAS BEEN ADVISED OF OR IS OTHERWISE AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LIABILITY ASSOCIATED WITH ANY VIRUSES WHICH MAY INFECT A USER’S COMPUTER EQUIPMENT OR RELATED SOFTWARE.
5. LIMITED LIABILITY.
IN NO EVENT SHALL GSB, ANY THIRD PARTY PROVIDER, OR ANY VENDOR BE LIABILE TO USER OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING , BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOST PROFITS, TRADING LOSSES OR DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM INCONVENIENCE, DELAY OR LOSS OF THE USE OF THE MATERIALS, PRODUCTS, OR SERVICE) ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THESE WEB SITE RULES OR ANY APPLICABLE SERVICE AGREEMENT, EVEN IF GSB OR SUCH THIRD PARTY PROVIDER OR VENDOR HAS BEEN ADVISED OF OR IS OTHERWISE AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY THEREOF, EXCEPT AS LIMITED BY APPLICABLE LAW. NO ACTION REGARDLESS OF FORM ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT MAY BE BROUGHT BY YOU MORE THAN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION HAS ACCRUED.
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold GSB and its Third Party Providers and Vendors harmless from and against any and all claims, losses, liability, cost, and expenses (including, but not limited to, reasonable attorneys’ fees) arising from your violation or breach of these Web Site Rules, any Service Agreement, any third party’s rights, including, but not limited to, copyrights, proprietary and privacy rights, or any applicable federal, state or local law, regulation or ordinance. Your obligations under this Section will survive the termination of these Web Site Rules, any applicable Service Agreement, or any Services.
7. TERMINATION OF SERVICE.
GSB reserves the right to deny or terminate your access to or use of the Site, any Service, Product, or Material or any portion thereof, in GSB’s sole discretion, without notice and without limitation, for any reason whatsoever including, but not limited to, your breach of any provision of these Web Site Rules or any applicable Service Agreement or discontinuance of GSB’s access to any Product or Material. In the event of any such termination by GSB, GSB shall have no liability to you.
8. CHANGE IN WEB SITE RULES.
GSB reserves the right to revise these Web Site Rules at any time by posting the revised Web Site Rules on the Site, and you are deemed to be apprised of and bound by any changes to these Web Site Rules unless you notify GSB of your objection to and refusal to accept the changes by sending written notice of such objection to GSB at: Gorham Savings Bank, Call Center, 10 Wentworth Drive, Gorham, Maine 04038 and include your name as it appears on your Account, social security number, account number, telephone number, and sign and date your correspondence. However, if you continue to access or use the GSB Web Site, or any Service, Product or Material, such action shall constitute your acceptance and agreement to the changes in the GSB Web Site Rules, notwithstanding any written notice of objection to the contrary.
9. COLLECTION OF NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
Like most websites, our website may incorporate “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” or similar tracking technologies, and “cookies” that allow us to track the actions of visitors of our website. This technology is used to collect non-personally identifiable information, such as the name of your Internet service provider, the IP address of the computer you are using, the type of browser software and operating system that you use, the date and time you access our website, the website address, if any, from which you linked directly to our website, the website address, if any, to which you travel from our website, your homepage customization preferences, your activity on various website pages and other similar traffic-related information.
We may aggregate your information with similar data collected from other visitors to help us improve our website and the products, services, applications, content and features that we provide through our website. We do not use non-personally identifiable information in any way to create or maintain a personal profile of you or collect personally identifiable information from you.
Tracking information we collect may be used in order to serve additional ads to you through various ad networks that can take advantage of this tracking technology (such as cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, etc.). Third party vendors, including but not limited to Google Ad Networks and Facebook, may show our ads on other sites that you visit based on past visitation behaviors. You can learn more and may opt-out of this tracking technology by visiting http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).
Google Analytics uses “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.
Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.
This website may use other third party tracking services such as HotJar and Visual Website Optimizer. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request. This data is collected for the purpose of analyzing and improving website visitor experiences. For information on how HotJar and Visual Website Optimizer collect and use your information, please refer to their privacy policies. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data by these third parties in accordance with their privacy policies.
You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
10. COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION VIA CONTACT FORMS AND SURVEYS
This website may collect Personal Information from you when you voluntarily complete a survey or fill out our contact form. You may opt out of providing your Personal Information in these situations by not entering it when asked.
11. CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COOPA)
Protecting Children’s Privacy Online:  This website is not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that these individuals do not provide Personal Information through the website. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 without parental consent.  Visit the Federal Trade Commission website for more information about the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).
You’re leaving the Gorham Savings Bank Website
The external site you are going to is not operated by Gorham Savings Bank, and may have a privacy policy that differs from that which is followed by Gorham Savings Bank. We are not responsible for the content of this external site.
Cancel
Continue
